So you can imagine now
I've got another mechanism.
I've got another way,
not just processing,
not just cooling
rate, but chemistry
to mess with this curve.
Because you can
imagine now that I
might be able to get to lower
and lower transition points.
You see this?
I might be able to get to lower
and lower transition points
if these things can move faster
and not get locked into a solid
as easily if I add more and
more of these chemical scissors.
So maybe this one, now instead
of being cooled slower, maybe
this one had more
soda than this one.
Maybe now they're
cooled at the same rate
but I've changed the
amount of impurities,
the amount of oxygen, O2- very
specifically, that I've put in.
So it's another way now
to change this curve.
Now, these are called--
the thing that forms
the glass-- and we're
really only talking about
silica as our glass.
You can make other types of
glass not made from silica.
We're talking about
silica in this class.
So silicon is the atom that
is making those long spaghetti
strands, and it's called
the network former.
Silicon is called